sm brother or role like most powerful mine under planet
sm兄弟或类似地球下最强大的地雷的角色
yet as opposed to many of is succes earth en reed assesseurs
但是与许多成功专家相反的是
marcus aurelius a virtuous lyonne to live consistently critters that attack the
marcus aurelius一个良性的利昂人，一贯活着的小动物袭击了
philosophical scroll colts toast and part of piece philosophy is da butt
哲学小马驹敬酒，而部分哲学是大屁股
type keep all my mind sm effect the stoves believe that you human in
类型也让我全神贯注sm效果炉灶相信你是人类
estate of flourishing hesitate to happiness
蓬勃发展的财产对幸福犹豫不决
you should always go to give there was a european
你应该总是去给一个欧洲人
not lusten c marcus aurelius was a bizim and carrying the burden of
不是lusten c marcus aurelius是bizim并承担着重担
leadership over an empire and all the stress that
对帝国的领导以及所有的压力
comes from this is word meditations gibsons and idea of ​​how i buy
来自这个是单词冥想吉布森和我如何购买的想法
Marcus Aurelius is famous for his negative visualization of what you mud and
马库斯·奥雷留斯（Marcus Aurelius）以他对泥浆和泥浆的负面观察而闻名
stro x us and meditative practice to start the dcf short seperate video by
stro x us和冥想练习通过以下方式开始dcf简短独立视频：
this out like to focus on is a lesson journaux teachings the weekend users
这个喜欢重点关注的是周末用户的课程journaux教学
practical advice for more tranquil life's the first one is very simple doe
实用建议，让生活更安静第一个是非常简单的能源部
lesson is a no-brainer right in order to be can be calmer
上课是明智的，才能变得更冷静
case zzimply pushing les now it's important to mention
案件现在正忙着推销文件，重要的是要提到
that the steam melted productivity and high regard
蒸汽融化了生产力并受到高度重视
sd css effort you to be in desserts on the other hand moderation is a
SD CSS的努力，另一方面，你要在甜点中节制
virtual so alex agnew should be target lesson when suppose to be
虚拟的，因此当alex agnew应该是目标课程时
industries marcus aurelius surfs with people too many things that are
行业marcus aurelius与人们一起冲浪太多了
necessary in the current age who and factions to almost unlimited
在当今时代所必需的人和派系几乎是无限的
entertainment something like this very easy to get caught up in all chance or man products or
像这样的娱乐活动很容易被所有机会或人的产品所吸引，或者
activities was doing les marcus of us also meant interpreter in less money
活动在为我们做事，这也意味着翻译费用更少
conversations arm nonsensical lead to nowhere and only waist of time
对话无意义导致无处可去
and energy this is how you do mains doing the essential
和能量这就是您做主电源的方式
and in the essential not only means at week old the cuff what if u
而且从本质上来说，这不仅意味着袖口一周，如果您
dat who work more intelligent lee and efficiently
谁可以更有效地工作，更高效
hb advantage that week one for this besides tranquility this weekend is your
HB的好处是，除了周末，这个周末的第一周是您的
lesson do better that essential consistently
一堂课做得更好，始终如一
take some mindful approach a quote if you can eliminate this
如果可以消除这种情况，请采取一些谨慎的方法报价
your have more time and more tranquility ask yourself at every moment this is
你有更多的时间和更多的宁静，每时每刻都问自己
necessary between do not want in my sns sharia simpsons as well to eliminate the
之间不要在我的鼻中也需要消除
and necessary actions that follow and close up shoot got it that helps to
并采取必要的行动并进行近距离拍摄，这有助于
stay focused on a daily endeavors is a measurement and list or at home the night before
专注于日常工作是一项测量和清单，或者在前一天晚上在家
this way way primary time to do is mayhew when you caught up in it
这样，当您陷入困境时，主要的时间就是可能
the morning what you come to effect on the mind
早上你会影响你的思想
picasso whose designer baby forehand der zwan laughing for the mind to worry
毕加索的设计师婴儿正手der zwan为担心而发笑
about two shorts s capes in another video hi folks plants too
在另一个视频中大约两个短裤的披风大家好，植物也一样
occasional bumps from traveling for recreational purposes and
出于休闲目的而偶尔旅行引起的颠簸
you see this good way to seek tranquility
你看到寻求安宁的好方法
the reasons for that is that whatever wiggle or even or even so the
这样做的原因是，无论摆动还是什至如此，
effect of traveling a lonely temporary that retirement is the novelty subsites will
退休是新奇的子网站将导致一个孤独的临时旅行的影响
confronted with a roman sahrawis was crippled of people
面对一个罗马的撒哈拉人被残废的人
seeking refuge from daily words by traveling or
寻求日常旅行的避难所或
designing and quite places like the mountains of beecher's
设计和漂亮的地方，如Beecher's的山脉
in his mind this was an india big thing to do because my fishie travel
在他看来，这是印度要做的一件大事，因为我的钓鱼之旅
one week and get away by going live in nowhere you go is more peaceful more
一个星期，走到无处走走，变得更安静
free of interruptions than your own soul that side there
没有干扰，没有那边那边的自己的灵魂
or in rhoon with change of scenery once in a while to
或偶尔在风光rh绕的隆隆山脉中
facilitate a mental cane cane islam so i keep these escapes basic en
促进精神拐杖伊斯兰教的精神，所以我保持这些逃脱基本en
letter was marcus aurelius by mail your cornmeal or meditation on there apps mode
信是marcus aurelius，是在该应用程序模式下通过邮件发送了您的玉米面或冥想
of reflection and contemplation in order to renew yourself to weaken coli portion
反思和沉思，以更新自己以削弱大肠杆菌含量
tardelli life's idea first two things to panda rover evoque youstoub reviewer
塔德利（Tardelli）生活的想法给熊猫漫游者（Evoque Youstoub）评论家带来了前两件事
treaty no mind icloud one that things have no dog school
条约没关系icloud一事无成
December and moving out side the disturbance could be sony van wim from her
十二月，搬到一边，可能是范·威姆（Sony Van Wim）离开她
uncle perceptions and 2 that there is one you see with already by then
叔叔的看法和2到那时你已经看到了
a success think of how many changes you already
成功想想您已经进行了多少更改
seen the world is nothing but change or life is only perception and close
看到世界不过是变化，而生活只是感知和亲密
which brings to the next piece of vice witjes
这带来了下一个副机智
remembering that if shall pass the stick sar infamous for remembering defining
记住如果通过了sar臭名昭著的记住定义
reality of life guards in twente buy memento mori least the remembrance of
特温特救生员的现实至少要记住
at home the ultimate acceptance that I have
在家里，我拥有终极的接受
changing nature of the universe also means the the gray and finishing of er
宇宙本质的变化也意味着er的灰色和光洁度
even mobistar lifestyle hissed keep in mind
即使是mobistar的生活方式也要牢记
half past four tanks passes by we can be merged and champing in one moment and in
四辆坦克经过的一半我们可以在瞬间融合在一起并获得冠军
the next moment it could be something totally different transcom a glow in
下一刻它可能是完全不同的Transcom焕发光芒
the blink of an eye and through my look at the history of this planet
眨眼间，通过我对这个星球的历史的了解
human life is just a tiny little hiccup in this cosmac evolution
在宇宙的进化过程中，人类的生活只是个小小的障碍
defective everything is a phlox could be a source or a site you can
有缺陷的一切都是福禄考可能是一个来源或网站，你可以
depend on stable and they finally you will be separated from their positions
依靠稳定，他们最终您将与他们的职位分离
and loved is with the camp your source of chrome is
和爱是与营地，您的铬来源
realization that everything stamped very nice and there is no point in being too
意识到一切都非常好，而且没有意义
good times and being strong leo first to bad times
美好的时光，坚强的狮子座到不幸的时光
happiness is a relatively and even a prezi
幸福是相对甚至是珍贵的
der good and bad ice and equally millionaires experience i joy and suffering this who
不论好坏，百万富翁也同样经历着我的快乐和痛苦，
is there in a world that is the wiper siphon live situation and how you react
在世界上有刮水器虹吸现场状况以及您如何反应
to that is also in phlox but about who can influence
在福禄考中也是如此，但是关于谁可以影响
howie react to change zo live shoot destiny concern so much esmarke sorry
Howie对改变zo live Shoot命运的反应做出了如此强烈的对不起
liz rood die infiniti of past and future games before has such a thing was that
莉兹·罗德（Liz rood）在过去和未来的游戏中死于英菲尼迪，之前曾发生过这样的事情：
we cannot see so good sign i get to feel self importance for this dress or
我们看不到这么好兆头，我开始觉得这件衣服的重要性，或者
any indignation item and whizzed a lot of star details
任何愤慨的物品，并闪过很多明星的细节
thank you for watching [Music]
谢谢您的收看[音乐]